<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <!-- Pager view label -->
    <string name="pager_label">Popular Tourists Spots</string>

    <!-- Introductory text Strings -->
    <string name="intro_text_1">Hello there toursits!</string>
    <string name="intro_text_2">Welcome to Abuja, the capital city of Nigeria.
        There are a lot of places to visit, and this App will help you with some of our fantastic locations.</string>
    <string name="intro_text_3">So Click This Button and Lets Begin</string>

    <!-- Landmark text Strings -->
    <string name="zuma_rock_heading">Zuma Rock</string>
    <string name="zuma_rock_description">Commonly referred to as the gateway between Abuja and Suleja,
        this large monolith in Niger State,Nigeria.
        it is composed of gabbro and granodiorite, and stands at a height of 725 metres.
        It was used for a defensive retreat by the Gbagyi people against invading neighbouring
        tribes during intertribal warring.</string>
    <string name="aso_rock_heading">Aso Rock</string>
    <string name="aso_rock_description">At a height of 400 metre, this monolith is one of the city\'s
        most noticeable feature,situated at the Asokoro district of Abuja.
        around it are the Nigerian Presidential Complex, Nigerian National Assembly,
        and Nigerian Supreme Court, the most important government structures in Nigeria.</string>
    <string name="millenium_park_heading">Millenium Park</string>
    <string name="milennium_park_description">The Millennium Park is the largest public park of Abuja,
        and is located in the Maitama district of the city.
        One side on the Park is dedicated to uncontaminated nature.
        In a system of terraces at different levels are located Nigeria\'s mountain vegetation, Savanna,
        Deciduous forest, Rainforest and brushwood as well as greenhouses for butterflies and tropical birds.
        The other side, corresponding to the main entrance from road, is dedicated to
        the scientific knowledge of the natural environment.</string>
    <string name="abuja_national_mosque_heading">Abuja National Mosque</string>
    <string name="abuja_national_mosque_description">The Abuja National Mosque, also known as the Nigerian National Mosque,
        is the national mosque of Nigeria.The mosque was built in 1984 and is open to the non-Muslim public, except during
        congregational prayers.The mosque is located in the capital city, Abuja, and is situated on Independence Avenue,
        across from the National Christian Centre. It includes a library and a conference room.</string>

    <!-- Restaurants text Strings -->
    <string name="_355_steakhouse_and_lounge_heading">355 Steakhouse and Lounge</string>
    <string name="_355_steakhouse_and_lounge_description">Located at 38, Osun street, off IBB Way, this restaurant, headed by
        Chef Michel Paris Jr and head Chef Steve Grove promises to tantalize your taste buds with the ines of steaks this
        side of abuja. it has an indoor restaurant and an outdoor lounge, where you can eat and take in the mesmerising view of Abuja</string>
    <string name="chez_victor_heading">Chez Victor</string>
    <string name="chez_victor_description">if you are looking to, as the french say, \"mettre du piment dans sa vie\",
        then look no further than Chez Victor.They serve delicious, authentic French cuisine- I recommend ordering the
        steak. The place is small and intimate which makes it perfect for romantic dinners for two. In addition to the
        lovely decor the service is also very good. As you can imagine all this comes at a price. Chez Victor is expensive
        but it\'s definetly worth it.</string>
    <string name="chopsticks_heading">Chopsticks</string>
    <string name="chopsticks_description">If you are looking for the best in terms of Asian
        cuisine in Abuja,then look no further than Chopsticks. Situated at Mississipi Street
        Maitama, this restaurants serves a large selection o cuisines, from the finest dumplings,
        to the spiciest curry, all the way to the classic ramen fusion.</string>
    <string name="obudu_grill_house_heading">Obudu Grill House</string>
    <string name="obudu_grill_house_description">Enjoy the variety of grilled foods and barbequed
        foods such as Cowboy Rib Eye, New York Strip Loin and Prime Fillet cuts. Located in Nigeria\'s
        capital city, Abuja. Obudu Grill Restaurant boast of having one of the been one of the best steak
        houses in Abuja with a unique dining experience that serves the finest steak cuts and grills prepared right before your eyes.</string>


    <!-- Malls text Strings -->
    <string name="ceddi_plaza_heading">Ceddi Plaza</string>
    <string name="ceddi_plaza_description">This was built in 2004. It is notable as one of the landmarks of Abuja city
        because of its imposing structure.One of the first modern shopping complex in Nigeria, Ceddi Plaza, like fine
        wine, keeps getting better with time with movie theaters, a bookstore, wine shop, grocery, restaurants, pharmacy,
        events hall and so much more present in it.</string>
    <string name="dunes_center_heading">Dunes Center</string>
    <string name="dunes_center_description">Carefully chosen to define luxury, Dunes Center is one of the most well
        reputed shopping malls in Nigeria. It incorporates everything from original antiques and gift shops to quality
        boutiques, as well as a supermarket, pastry shop and restaurant.</string>
    <string name="silverbird_entertainment_center_heading">Silverbird Entertainment Center</string>
    <string name="silverbird_entertainment_center_description">This intimidating and magnificent entertainment center is the crowning
        glory of the Silverbird Group and one of the most popular shopping malls in Abuja.This 33,000 square metre retail structure
        comprise of a 4-storey building. The ground and first floors are reserved for shopping stores, a lifestyle center for the
        second floor, a 12 screen cinema for the third floor and the fourth floor is for penthouse rooms.</string>
    <string name="the_capital_hub_heading">The Capital Hub</string>
    <string name="the_capital_hub_description">The Capital Hub provides a diverse range of exclusive retail shops as well
        as some executive offices in addition to top leisure and family entertainment.The wide range of retail shops cutting
        across different sectors and the variety of different entertainment offerings makes The Capital Hub a most desired
        spot for fun seekers and business executives alike.</string>

    <!-- Hotels text Strings -->
    <string name="transcorp_hilton_heading">Transcorp Hilton Abuja</string>
    <string name="transcorp_hilton_description">Transcorp Hilton Abuja is a 4-Star, state of the art, hotel located at
        1 Aguiyi Ironsi Street, Maitama, Abuja.Transcorp Hilton Abuja has 670 luxuriously decorated rooms and offers
        complimentary breakfast, all-day snacks and refreshment, cocktails, local/international newspapers and magazines
        to all guests.The hotel has 7 restaurants and bars with a wide range of international and local cuisine coupled
        with a selection of the best wines and cocktails.</string>
    <string name="fraser_suites_heading">Fraser Suites Abuja</string>
    <string name="fraser_suites_description"><![CDATA[Fraser Suites Abuja is nestled in the heart of the modern
     Federal Capital of Nigeria. The newly opened Fraser Suites features 126 Gold-Standard residences that combine
      comfort, style & technology with outstanding facilities and exclusive in-house services.Each room features a
      spacious bathroom, king-sized beds, cable connected LCD TV sets, refrigerators and air conditioners.]]></string>
    <string name="sheraton_hotel_heading">Sheraton Abuja Hotel</string>
    <string name="sheraton_hotel_description">Located in the classy Maitama area of Abuja, it provides tasteful
        accommodation options to its guests. The rooms on the top levels offer a beautiful view of the elegant
        Abuja city.It offers round-the-clock front desk service, concierge, and car rental services.</string>
    <string name="bon_hotel_heading">BON Hotel Abuja</string>
    <string name="bon_hotel_description">An imposing architectural masterpiece with a perfect touch of class,
        the BON Hotel is elegantly nestled close to Abuja\'s city centre.The 28 well-appointed luxury rooms
        available in the hotel are categorised into Classic, Executive and Loft Suites. A gourmet restaurant
        serves mouth-watering buffet breakfast, and delicious lunch and dinner complimented with an exotic bar
        stocked with all kinds of assorted drinks.</string>



</resources>
